Hey, Shailendra.
Hi, Karuna.
Yeah.
Good morning. Good evening.
Hey, Rob, how are you?
Hello, Team. How's everybody?
Hi, everyone.
Yeah, you did.
There we go.
Hey, Eric, I realized that I had signed up with my Gmail account rather than using my Bounteous, and I'm trying to connect my clod code to your Figma so that when you guys share Christina's designs, I can pull them out and then, as I do my design stuff where I can fill in the middle. So I'm just trying to get all that wired up now. So if you can attach my e-mail, that would be great.
Yeah, we can do that.
When you get a chance, please, and thank you.
So this morning will be a little late, as mentioned. Last Friday was a holiday in India, and then this Friday is a holiday in India as well for a different group. And then Monday is then a day off for then the US side. So today is it will be a little late. Monday will be a little late. So basically we'll all see each other then again on Tuesday.
So while I have the mic, I might as well just talk now. I don't even know what I did yesterday.
I don't know, answered a lot of questions, been doing a lot of wiki things, prepping for, oh, that's right, I was prepping for the meeting today, which for the most part, the 1st 20 minutes are just going to be more just kind of throwing kudos at the team at the various things we've done. I'm also going to show where the application is right now. And then we'll do 20 minutes of going through the designs, 20, 30, whatever we need.
And then the last I was just going to say for any like feedback or questions. So it should be a pretty light session today. Because for the most part, I mean, we're just kind of getting the ground laid down, getting a lot of the rules laid out, just getting access to things. So and with that, I'll go ahead and pass it off to my team for just giving out some updates. So Karuna, if you want to go ahead and give your update.
Yeah, sure. So I was working on Scribble 28 user story. I have completed analysis. There were some questions, so I posted those today. I also worked upon 31, so I'll be adding some questions for that as well, mostly today. But yeah, I'm trying to like derive the test cases.
for both the user stories.
Yeah, that's all from me. Thank you.
Okay.
And as I said, make sure that you have Atlassian connection in your Claude desktop app. And then just let me know because I merged in those changes.
Mm.
In the meta repo, I had inadvertently, well, I didn't, but my operator put in some gates that were hard blocking the team to where I was the only one allowed to make changes to the backlog in Jira. So thankfully, Karuna told me that this morning, because my workflow, I add a lot of gates to things to make sure things don't happen. So I kind of gated the team out of being able to make changes. So that was not good.
Suren.
Yap.
No issues, yeah, we will check. Yeah, looks like I have to raise a request, like we will not have permissions to do it, so I just raised it before the call. Hopefully, it should be resolved by Monday.
OK, perfect.
Yeah, thank you.
And then just be sure to talk with the team too, so that everyone else gets on there too, because everyone's going to need this. So yeah, carry that forward. I'll make sure I'll put it on like the access list that Pramod created.
Uh, Chu, if you want to go.
Sure, Rob. Thank you. So, yesterday I was picking up this ticket, so I have posted my proposal regarding the device procurement, like how we should distribute the device and strategy. Now, we can start with a basic minimum version device and a single device as well, for now, for now, from the development perspective.
I can start with the emulators. So all the tech related setup has been done from my side. All both the emulators, Android and iOS, both are working at my end now. I don't see any challenge in running the code or doing the MVP related technical or development part.
So that is done. Second, I also picked up this Scribble 8 where I just posted some thoughts on the architectural part. It's more like a proposal. So I raised the PR in Meta Scribble app.
So I would leave it to Rob so that just give it a review and let me know if anything needs changes from your from your side or you have more inputs on it. I'll update. So coming to this table late, my thoughts is basically since we are going to be, I'm going to be working on both platforms.
So and I'm trying the strategy that both the since Android still not prioritized, but I will try that whichever I'm working on or which module I'm picking up. I'm trying to build it as close as possible on both platforms so that at any time we want to, you know, introduce Android.
We will have less turn of time to, you know, introduce Android side, like the code should be working in parallel for both the platforms, so I'll see if I can, you know, accommodate.
a bit of testing every time I push anything in the module that is working for both or not like that changes. So that's going to be a strategy for me now. And yeah, so that's how I have also added the architectural document in the scribble it.
So these are my thoughts on it. I'll also continue on the same tickets as Scribble 8, and once we have some discussions on their device procurement, I'll continue on Scribble 18. Next, I'm planning to pick the Scribble 76. So I see the Apple developer account has been set up properly, and I can also see one application has been created, the Scribble prod.
a named application. Just one thing on this one, like the scribble prod would appear on App Store. So do we want to show that app as scribble prod or only scribble for end users?
When it's just a metadata, we can change the title, but yeah.
I don't know, what do you recommend? Go, sorry, go ahead, Erik.
Who are you talking about? Yap.
I was just saying the name of the actual product itself. So I had set it up based on the doc that I got, but obviously we want it just to be scribble in the App Store.
Mmh.
Yeah, okay, no worries. And then what we can do is either we can create scribble only, and we keep it scribble only, and then once we are doing this test flight distribution, we do the testing part, everything, but once we are going to push, we can also change the name before, you know, submitting it for review and anything. So it is pretty much doable.
at later stages as well. For now, we can start with stable product and later on, before pushing anything to App Store, we'll just correct it out. This is one thing. Or we can set up two applications. One is purely for development and testing, purely separate instance of the application where we are pushing code in all testing. And once we have the finalized, we can do.
the production one, but the trade-off would be that we have to do 2 things at a time, like working with dev application and then pushing to production. There would be the challenge. But for now, I think we can start with only scribble. And as and when we required, we can do the changes as well. Like we can introduce an internal testing app.
Play that.
I was gonna say from what you were saying, does it make sense for it then for us to do something where we do like scribble dash dev or scribble dash something where that's the like prototype QA one and then we did just have scribble which is then our production one. So basically I'm taking the production off of it while giving us like the, you know, two different options, one for QA and testing and then while still having our production version one.
without the production word in it.
Yeah, yeah, basically introducing 2 applications would allow us to, you know, keep the things separate, first of all, so that anything that we are doing with MVP or, you know, progressing on that as well, we don't touch the production part. The production part, we can only push the final test date draft of the version.
That is one thing. We can still do with the same application, like single application and doing all this activity, but we have to be careful in that order. We don't need to push anything accidentally for review or something. That was the reason. Again, it totally depends if we want to, I mean, it's more like a decision you can take.
If we want to go ahead and do application or one, we can, we will be good with both.
Rob, just so I'm understanding this correctly, as we as we push out the beta to this test group of users, I assume. They're going to need to have. Their own. That's going to be essentially like a place to test that beta, correct? So that whatever we deliver them.
that's not going to change, improve. Am I understanding that properly?
Yeah, we're basically trying to create two output artifacts, one that is sort of like our testing and playground area where we push everything and it has like pretty much the latest feature sets. And then we'll have like the production one, which is the hardened pass through QA. Everything is good. Like we don't want to touch and we just only push like the best to it.
Yeah.
And where does the beta testing fall into that?
That would be the beta testing one, which would be that secondary one that we would have. And that's what everybody would be kind of playing with. And then as I said, then everybody would get the final one too, so they would almost have two versions. One would be, as I said, the like latest and greatest, and one is then like the production hardened one.
Into that time.
Gotcha. Okay.
Makes sense.
Awesome. Cool.
Yeah, if you want to write that up and then let's bring that in front of the team next week and then kind of decide from there. Because I don't want to make the decision right now. I want to write that up and then wait for the full team to get the whole decision, especially once the architect's back.
Yap.
Yeah.
Understood, Rob. Yeah, I'm going to write up a proposal document for that and explaining everything in detail, like what the benefits are and what are the trade-offs of turnout time for that, and then we can decide on that later on. So, yeah, that is the overall idea of things I'm having right now with these things.
Yeah, so that's the pretty much update from my side. Thank you.
Oh, something I forgotten, maybe that's what I did yesterday, but I also brought the meta repo into Scribble now. So Scribble now has the official latest and greatest meta repo. So now you guys have both the Scribble meta repo, and then you have then the official Scribble mobile app, which the team has already started to build out.
And so I said, I'll show today where it's at, which again, it's not done or even, you know, like there, but we have something in place.
Great. I don't know if Eric or Matt, do you guys have anything?
Awesome.
The only thing left for me to button up is I sent over Pramod the IAM user. I gave him an IAM user account so that he could get in and see what's going on with the AWS account. We have a scribble development organization created or account created within our organization.
The disconnect is how do I connect your team to that specific account? So I sent him over the info. He has a full IAM account. He can get in, take a look at things, and just take it from there.
OK, perfect.
Yap.
As you know, more likely he'll see that and then start it on Monday. So yeah, so we'll probably catch back up on Tuesday on that.
And I'll be around, I'll be around Sunday evening and probably most of the day Monday as well, so I'll be able to go back and forth with him on his time and and just get that done.
Perfect. Perfect. Thank you for doing that.
All right. Anyone have anything for after item?
after party, so I like to call it.
There were some questions which we were trying to ask yesterday for the browser stack and other details. Like, Erik, we have any details around that?
What was that again, Rob? Could you clarify that?
This is about the browser stack credentials if we have it, if your team has used them in the past. This is for running the automation test on different devices.
That I'm unsure of.
Okay.
Were there any other questions? Yeah, I don't know that they know anything about their browser stack implementation. Right. I remember, I think it's a, there's a testing framework that she's attempting to use. We'll pull in like a browser stack, which is, you know, Chrome, Safari, all the various ones, and then, you know, right, allow you to then run the test against those stacks.
Apologies.
Kirti.
Yeah, it's like just bring up the simulators as well. It will bring up real devices as well. So that we can run the test on that. Yeah, it basically it's a licensed tool.
Okay, so maybe write up the proposal on that of, you know, why we should use that one tool and then we can run it by them and then maybe they could get the licenses for us if we don't have them.
Yeah, happy to do that.
That's all.
Awesome. Well, if no one else has anything, then I will see Eric and Matt later on today, and the rest of you will see you next Tuesday.
I look forward to it. Happy holidays to you guys.
Happy holiday to everyone.
Thank you, Ben. Thank you. Thank you, everyone.
Nikhil.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
All right. Enjoy your weekend. Take care.
Bye-bye. Thank you.